Aaron Gehring

Email: aarongehring94@gmail.com Tel: 920-757-4758 Appleton, Wisconsin

A creative and concept-driven problem solver, currently enrolled in the Information Systems Security Specialist program at Fox Valley Technical College. Strong grasp of fundamental concepts that allow quick familiarization with new environments and fast learning.

SKILLS

Soft-skills	Soft-skills (cont.)	Security	Scripting	Operating Systems	Networks	Suites
Adaptability	Driven	Windows and Linux Server Security	Python	Linux	Windows Server 2012 & 2016	Google Suite
Articulate Communicator	Enterprising	Log Collection	SQL	Manjaro	Active Directory	Microsoft Office
Creativity	Inquisitive	Log Analysis and Reporting	Bash	Ubuntu	Group Policies	Office365
Critical Thinker	Problem-Solving	Incident Reporting	PowerShell	Windows	Cisco IOS	
Customer Service	Versatile	Risk Analysis	JavaScript		Firewall	
Diplomacy		SIEM	REST API		VPN	

PROJECTS

Analyst, Wireshark Analysis Project, Incident Response, Fox Valley Technical College (September 2021)

Performed an analysis of a provided Wireshark packet capture file originating from an infected PC. Wrote an incident report based on the findings of my analysis.

Analyst, Graylog SIEM Project, Security Monitoring & Operations, Fox Valley Technical College (April 2021)

Created a working SIEM infrastructure with Graylog and documented the process. Collaborated with group members to write a report summarizing and comparing different SIEM solutions.

Programmer, FIRST Robotics Competition (July 2013 — May 2017)

A yearly competition for high school students where a large robot is built by a team to complete tasks and compete against other robots. A part of Team 93 - NEW Apple Corps. Developed a web app and android app for live match scouting, a year learning Java to help write the autonomous operation code, and two years as a part of the marketing corp.

- 2017, As a part of the scouting corp, developed a web app and a simple, helper android app to record statistics for every match live.
- · Utilized Business Intelligence principles and techniques to win first place despite the team's low seed.
- 2014 Gracious Professionalism Award x2; 2015 Regional Winners, Entrepreneurship Award, Gracious Professionalism Award; 2016 Team Spirit Award, Gracious Professionalism Award; 2017 Regional Winners, Regional Engineering Inspiration x2

Engineering Design Competition Finalist, Project Lead the Way (2017)

A competition apart of our curriculum where my group of four classmates designed and developed a prototype product

EDUCATION

Information Systems Security Specialist, Associate Degree, Fox Valley Technical College (Anticipated December 2021)

EMPLOYMENT

Assistant Manager II, Route 41 Pizza, LLC (Domino's; Appleton, Wisconsin) (July 2018 — Present)

- Demonstrated adaptability by being the first to master Cutting Edge, a complete overhaul of the oven tending system.
- Identified and solved problems with point-of-sale, printer, and dispatch systems via troubleshooting.
- Employed creative solutions to mitigate impact of malfunctioning systems.
- · Achieved conflict resolution with customer complaints and with coworkers while maintaining a fair and honest attitude.
- Multitasked making food, helping customers, taking phone calls and oven tending.
- Improved our store's food usage variance 10x by improving availability of scales on makeline, as well as actively monitoring coworkers' portioning at the
 makeline or while oven tending.
- · Trained coworkers and a focus on continual improvement though process improvement or eliminating poor methods.
- An "ace" in every store zone.

IT Summer Intern, Appleton Area School District (June 2017 — September 2017)

Worked with the AASD IT department over the summer to get the computer systems ready for the next school year. Organized and rewired each school's server racks, cleaned and reimaged every computer and Chromebook. Created and organized an online directory of images for every room of each school. Verified the operation of computers and classroom peripherals, including projectors.